

## Profile

I'm a 24 year-old Argentinian software developer. I got my degree in the year 2019. I'm really passionate about developing software and I'm always updating my knowledge by reading official documentation, taking courses or learning from my colleagues.

I'm currently working as a full stack developer and taking some online courses, I'm really into learning about new technologies.

GitHub Profile: JavierAgustinAle

LinkedIn Profile: javieragustinale

# **Employment History**

Full Stack Software Developer, Sinergia Digital S.R.L, Neuquén, Argentina

JANUARY 2020 - PRESENT

Full stack developer working in a large-scale application for the local government.

Front-end: Angular & Typescript - Redux (NgRx), ng-bootstrap,ag-grid,Angular

Material.

Back-end: .NET, C#, ASP Web API.

Database: Oracle.

SCRUM

Git (GitLab)

Mantis Bug Tracker.

Web Developer (Intership), Ministry of Education, Cordoba, Córdoba, Argentina.

JUNE 2019 - DECEMBER 2020

Internship done while I was in my final year of college.

### Education

Degree Software Development, Technical Superior Institute , Cordoba, Argentina.

MARCH 2017 - DECEMBER 2019

Three years degree.

Average Score: 8.63 / 10

## Courses

First Certificate in English, University of Cambridge

FEBRUARY 2006 - NOVEMBER 2013

#### Details

Argentina

javierale25@live.com

NATIONALITY

Argentinean

25/01/1996

#### Skills

TypeScript

JavaScript

Angular

React

HTML & CSS

Oracle

C#

API Rest

Languages

Spanish

English